tjskl.org.cn 2017-11-04

# Privacy Policy of Our Site - About Us

Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

When you use our service, we may collect and use your related information. We hope that through the "privacy policy" ,when you using our services ,how do we collect, use, store this information , and how we can provide you with access, update, control, and protection of the information. This "privacy policy" is closely related to the services you use. I hope you can read it carefully, and make the appropriate choice according to the guidelines of this "privacy policy" when you need it. The related technology of the words "privacy policy", in order to understand,we try to express your concise and to the point.

 **Information Collecting**

When we provide services, we may collect, store and use the following information related to you. If you do not provide relevant information, may not be able to register as our users or can not enjoy some of the services we provide, or can not achieve the intended effect of the relevant services.

 **Information Providing**

In the account registration or use of our service, associated with the personal information you provide to us, such as phone numbers and e-mail; you through our services to other parties to provide information sharing, and you use our services stored information.

 **Information Using**

To provide you with our services;

When we provide services for authentication, customer service, security, fraud monitoring, archiving and backup purposes, to ensure that we provide you with the products and services security;

 **Information Sharing**

We may share your personal information

Used for the following purposes: 

-To provide you with our services;; 

\- To achieve the purpose of "how we might use information";

\- To fulfill our obligations and to exercise our rights in the "service agreement" or the "privacy policy";

\- Understanding, maintaining and improving our services.
